The brighter the star, the darker the truth.
The Mystery of Marilyn Monroe: The Unheard Tapes is a
documentary film directed by Emma Cooper.
This documentary explores the mystery surrounding the death of movie icon Marilyn
Monroe through previously unheard interviews with her inner circle.
Self, played by Anthony Summers.
Joan Greenson, played by Linzi Hateley.
Natalie Jacobs, played by CJ Johnson.
Hildi Greenson, played by Sorel Johnson.
Sydney Guilaroff, played by Andre Lillis.
Danny Greenson, played by Sion Lloyd.
The Mystery of Marilyn Monroe: The Unheard Tapes is a 2022 American
documentary film directed by Emma Cooper for Netflix.
It is centered on the life and untimely death of American actress and cultural icon Marilyn Monroe
and is told through archival footage and unseen interviews with friends of the star.
The film was released on April 27, 2022.
Between April 24, 2022 and May 8, 2022 the show was
watched for 22.95 million hours globally.
The film explores themes of interview, biography, archive
footage, found footage, hollywood star.